Dou demo ii sonna kao shite
Nothing matters anymore. Making that expression,
Yoki senu ame ni kokoro nurasu
my heart becomes drenched by the unexpected rain
Yami o kao ni nurita kuri hikari wo me ni yadoshi
Shadows paint my face. The light retained in my eyes
Ikita kokochi nado sezu ni
has lived without sentiment
Yeah!
Nee nani mo kamo narete ku no ka na
Hey I wonder if I could get used to everything
Kinou made no afureru namida mo
As for the overflowing tears of yesterday
Damashiteta kakushiteta nda koware sou na jibun wo
I’ve deceived you, and hid them away. Don’t let the nearly broken me
Mou kono mama barenai de jibun wo damashite
Show itself any further
Kuuru ni mune wo kogashite
Fooling myself. I coolly languished
Kono mayoi wo dou sureba ii no ka
What can I do with this hesitation?
Mou wakaranai kara wakaranakute ii
Because I don’t understand anymore, I don’t need to understand
Risuku ga aru kara takanaru shinzou wo kanji rareru
There’s a risk after all, I feel my heart throbbing
shinjita michi wo
along the road I believed in.
Tenchou Fansubs
mayou hougaku e
Towards the wavering direction