sankakkei o kuzushite
Destroy the triangle
hisomeru angou o yomitoru
Conceal the code
suraido saseteku
Slide your way in
puraido o tamotsu
and maintain your pride
atarashii katachi de kotae o michibiku
In your new shape guide yourself towards the answer
shinmokuhyou sekai o yatte, ikinokore!
Break the world of senses and survive!
mado kara sashikomu kibou no hikari ga
Cut through your actions. The light of hope,
kodoku o tsutsun de kage o kagayakasu
envelops loneliness. Illuminate the shadow
hitomi ha mirai to byakuya o toraeta
Capture the future in your eyes
jibun o shinji te jibun o ayatsure!
Believe in freedom, Control yourself.